// let questionsArr = [
//     {
//       "type": "multiple",
//       "difficulty": "easy",
//       "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
//       "question": "Which Pok&eacute;mon can learn the move &quot;Secret Power&quot; by leveling up?",
//       "correct_answer": "Audino",
//       "incorrect_answers": [
//         "Type:Null",
//         "Arceus",
//         "Silvally"
//       ]
//     },
//     {
//       "type": "multiple",
//       "difficulty": "easy",
//       "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
//       "question": "Which of these is not a wonder weapon in &quot;Call Of Duty: Zombies&quot;?",
//       "correct_answer": "R115 Resonator",
//       "incorrect_answers": [
//         "GKZ-45 Mk3",
//         "Ray Gun",
//         "Scavenger"
//       ]
//     },
//     {
//       "type": "multiple",
//       "difficulty": "easy",
//       "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
//       "question": "What is the main ship used by Commander Shepard in the Mass Effect Franchise called?",
//       "correct_answer": "Normandy",
//       "incorrect_answers": [
//         "Osiris",
//         "Infinity",
//         "Endeavour"
//       ]
//     },
//     {
//       "type": "multiple",
//       "difficulty": "easy",
//       "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
//       "question": "Pok&eacute;mon Go is a location-based augmented reality game developed and published by which company?",
//       "correct_answer": "Niantic",
//       "incorrect_answers": [
//         "Rovio",
//         "Zynga",
//         "Supercell"
//       ]
//     },
//     {
//       "type": "multiple",
//       "difficulty": "easy",
//       "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
//       "question": "In which year was League of Legends released?",
//       "correct_answer": "2009",
//       "incorrect_answers": [
//         "2010",
//         "2003",
//         "2001"
//       ]
//     },
//     {
//       "type": "multiple",
//       "difficulty": "easy",
//       "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
//       "question": "In the &quot;Hitman&quot; series, what is the name of the main character?",
//       "correct_answer": "Agent 47",
//       "incorrect_answers": [
//         "Agent 27",
//         "Agent Smith",
//         "Agent 67"
//       ]
//     },
//     {
//       "type": "multiple",
//       "difficulty": "easy",
//       "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
//       "question": "Which game did NOT get financed via Crowdfunding?",
//       "correct_answer": "Enter the Gungeon",
//       "incorrect_answers": [
//         "Town of Salem",
//         "Undertale",
//         "Tower Unite"
//       ]
//     },
//     {
//       "type": "multiple",
//       "difficulty": "easy",
//       "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
//       "question": "Who is the writer of the game &quot;Half-Life&quot;?",
//       "correct_answer": "Marc Laidlaw",
//       "incorrect_answers": [
//         "Gabe Newell",
//         "Robin Walker",
//         "Chet Faliszek"
//       ]
//     },
//     {
//       "type": "multiple",
//       "difficulty": "easy",
//       "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
//       "question": "In what year was the game &quot;FTL: Faster Than Light&quot; released?",
//       "correct_answer": "2012",
//       "incorrect_answers": [
//         "2014",
//         "2013",
//         "2011"
//       ]
//     },
//     {
//       "type": "multiple",
//       "difficulty": "easy",
//       "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
//       "question": "The &quot;Day of Defeat&quot; series of games take place during which war?",
//       "correct_answer": "World War II",
//       "incorrect_answers": [
//         "World War I",
//         "Vietnam War",
//         "Iraq War"
//       ]
//     }
//   ]